primedia.co.za 2016-03-24

# Primedia | Privacy Policy

Primedia (Pty) Ltd and its group companies and any successor operators of its business are sensitive to your privacy interests and believe that the protection of those interests is a significant responsibility. This policy explains how we will handle the personal information you provide to us and what we learn about you from your visit to our web site.

By using this site, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy.  If you do not agree to our Privacy Policy then please do not use this site.

**What is personal information?**

In order to provide you with the services offer Primedia (Pty) Ltd on this site, you may be required by Primedia (Pty) Ltd to provide Primedia (Pty) Ltd with personal information.  Personal information is information which identifies you as an individual, including but not limited to, your name and contact details.

**How we obtain information about you**

The information we collect about you varies depending upon which part of the web site you visit and how you interact with it.  Information about you may be collected without you being aware of it.

**Information which you are aware we collect**

On our pages you can update personal details, make requests, view information, and submit information and register to receive services or materials.  The types of personal information collected on these pages are name; title; place of work; work address; e-mail address; phone number; career category and areas of interest.

We do not acquire more information about you than is necessary for us to provide our services efficiently.

**What we do with your information**

As a general rule the information which you supply will be processed purely for the purposes for which it is supplied and collected, specifically Primedia (Pty) Ltd will use this your personal information to contact you regarding, for example, career related matters. We ensure all our employees are aware of their responsibilities to protect your privacy and we only give access to your data to the employees who need to access it.

However, we may on occasion use and transfer your information to our group companies for the following purposes: (a) for business development; (b) market research; (c) to provide you with details of promotions, products, offers and services; (d) to share it between us and our group companies for direct marketing purposes.

We will not transfer your information to other third parties without your consent unless it is required of Primedia (Pty) Ltd by law.

We understand that not everybody likes to receive direct marketing.  If you do not wish to receive direct marketing information, please tell us by contacting us on the details given at the end of this policy.  In addition, each time we send you marketing information by e-mail or SMS text messaging, we will provide an opportunity for you to unsubscribe from receiving further information from us.

Also, if we sell our company or part of it, we will share your information with the purchaser, who may then provide you with information on their products and services. If you do not consent to such transfers, please do not subscribe to our services.

**Information which you are not aware we collect**

We may use “Cookies” and other types of tracking software in order to personalise your visit to our web site and enhance the experience by gaining a better understanding of your particular interests and customizing our pages for you. A cookie is a message given to a web browser by a web server and which is then stored by Primedia (Pty) Ltd by the browser in a text file. Each time the browser requests a page from the server this message is sent back which enables the user to be identified.

We may use the information provided by cookies to analyse trends, administer the site, or for research and marketing purposes to help us better serve you.  No information which personally identifies you will be collected through the cookies.  If you like, you can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie so you have the chance to accept it and you can also set your browser to turn off all cookies.  The web site <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/> (run by the Interactive Marketing Bureau) contains step-by-step guidance on how cookies can be switched off by users.

**How we protect the information we process**

We have put in place measures which ensure the security of the information we collect and its correct use. These are appropriate to the nature of the information and prevent unauthorised access. We take reasonable steps to ensure the reliability of our own staff and ensure that any persons who process information on our behalf reach the same high standards that we set ourselves and limit their access to your data to what is necessary in order for them to perform their roles and responsibilities. Our security measures include the use of software firewalls, encryption and intrusion detection systems. We store transaction information on secure computers located in locked data centres to which only selected employees have access.  We will ask for your express permission before we use your personal information for any purpose not disclosed above.

**The accuracy of your information**

While we endeavour to ensure that the information we hold about you is accurate and, where necessary, kept up to date, we shall assume that in the absence of evidence to the contrary, the information you provide us with is accurate.  .  We will provide you with access to your personal information and make every effort to provide you with access to your registration data so that you may view, update or correct your information (see below under heading “Access Rights”).  To protect your privacy, we will also take steps to verify your identity before granting you access to your personal information.  You may also update or correct your personal information held by Primedia (Pty) Ltd by writing to us at [info@Primedia.co.za ](mailto:info@Primedia.co.za%20)or at the address provided in the Contact Us section on the site.  We do not retain any information about you which is out of date or which is no longer required by Primedia (Pty) Ltd.

**Links**

Our web-site contains links to other web sites belonging to third parties.  We do not control the privacy practices of these other sites.  You should therefore make sure, when you leave our site that you have read that site’s privacy policy.

**Changes to the Policy**

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify, add or remove sections of this Privacy Policy at any time and any changes will be notified to you using the e-mail address you have given us or by an announcement on this site.  Your continued use of this site, following the posting of changes to these terms, will mean you accept these changes.

**Access Rights**

You have a right to access the personal data we hold about you.  If you wish to obtain a copy of this information, please write to us at the details given below enclosing your postal details.

**Privacy Queries**

If you have any questions regarding this policy, or you wish to update your details or remove your personal data from our records, please contact us at info@Primedia.co.za or at the address provided in the Contact Us section on the site.

**Which Laws Apply**

This Privacy Policy will be governed by the laws of South Africa.  You consent to the jurisdiction of the South African courts for any dispute which may arise out of this privacy policy.

Thank you for visiting our site.
